Raymond Clapper Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Reference File, 1913-1962 (Box 99-256)
  - Wyoming, 1938-1940
  - Youngstown, Ohio, 1939